>Typesetting
--Fighting Arena (clip) (52)
#1
tIIzLk?S
m;ABobpD
a!GhNsvw
xgw0!5wL
lk'aux8k
3J5dmyy;
l'3,8yW5
pKP2DWrW
Fighting Arena
#2
1Uvo1O
c:KO'2
JUP6dA
nftnlE
Zjl!vF
C?l53Z
GZmhvb
u'8cw?
2F   CH6
#3
JN't?9aw
a9WBvk:W
gN0FV2FH
zzAv8.nY
p;WNMaN?
7QT.fS:d
Wv3Nw?Nm
DMSC;'ia
2F  CH1
#4
,s;CY9M!
B?Q?UF4H
fkTo;2XS
xiwGw1LT
0XNIdrzR
G4GCrirE
WYNvKuKD
iGO4.eEV
2F
JN't?9aw
a9WBvk:W
gN0FV2FH
zzAv8.nY
p;WNMaN?
7QT.fS:d
Wv3Nw?Nm
DMSC;'ia
tIIzLk?S
m;ABobpD
a!GhNsvw
xgw0!5wL
lk'aux8k
3J5dmyy;
l'3,8yW5
pKP2DWrW
1Uvo1O
c:KO'2
JUP6dA
nftnlE
Zjl!vF
C?l53Z
GZmhvb
u'8cw?
1Uvo1O
c:KO'2
JUP6dA
nftnlE
Zjl!vF
C?l53Z
GZmhvb
u'8cw?
2F   CH6
1Uvo1O
c:KO'2
JUP6dA
nftnlE
Zjl!vF
C?l53Z
GZmhvb
u'8cw?
--Ep Title
Episode 53
Cog
--Kirara doesn't believe us!
Kirara doesn't
believe us!
--No way!
No way!
#1
#2
No way!
--Bottom text
Cross Theory
Rock-Paper-Scissors Theory
Stamp Rally Theory
--Rule 9
Players who do not show any change in points within 19 days of joining or acquiring points
shall be stripped of their technique.
Players shall be able to view the following information on other players:
name, points, number of rules added, and current colony.
Culling Game Player: Kashimo Hajime
--Next Ep
Next Episode
Tokyo Colony No. 1, Part 1